

ANANDA BINTANG **SAPUTRA**

Sidoarjo, Indonesia 085330632334 anandabintang4@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Accomplished Full Stack Developer versed in both front-end and back-end coding for Information System sites. Expert in handling full software development lifecycle with focus on quality, security and usability. Brings great multitasking and problem-solving abilities combined with advanced optimization and advanced coding skills.

SKILLS

- Programming Language : HTML,
 Programming Framework : CSS, PHP, Javascript
- Website Optimization
- Database Development
- Bootstrap, Codeigniter, Laravel,
- Team Collaboration

NodeJS, ExpressJS

- Databases : MySQL, PostgreSQL
- Version Control Systems: Git, Github

EXPERIENCE

Junior Full Stack Developer Internship | Malang, Indonesia March 2023 - September 2023

- Collaborated with designers and development teams to create high-quality interactive web experiences.
- Wrote, organized and distributed technical documentation.
- Evaluated application responsiveness and eliminated bugs and glitches.
- Completed training programs to learn new coding languages and application developments.

Junior Full Stack Developer Internship | Sidoarjo, Indonesia

September 2021 - December 2021

- Completed training programs to learn new coding languages and application developments.
- Consulted with teams and supported users throughout full life cycle of software product development.
- Wrote, organized and distributed technical documentation.
- Developed Application Programming Interface and back-end applications.
- Evaluated application responsiveness and eliminated bugs and glitches.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) - Informatics Telkom Surabaya Insitute of Technology, Surabaya

September 2023 - Now

High School - Software Engineering SMK Antartika 2, Sidoarjo

August 2020 - June 2023

- Member of Software Engineering Extra Curricular
- Participants in the District Level Web Technology Student Competency Competition

LANGUAGE

English Intermediate (B1) Indonesia

Proficient (C2)